filecloud.io 2012-12-19

# privacy policy - filecloud.io

###  Information collected by filecloud.io 

filecloud.io uses cookies and other data sent by your browser to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use filecloud.io services in order to improve the quality of our services. The following information may be collected and stored: 

  * Your geographic country code (eg US,UK,IT etc) is determined from your network address (specific ip addresses are never logged since there is no need) on uploads and downloads, this is collected and stored for up to a month in order to better understand the needs of users across the globe.
  * Email addresses are recorded and verified on registration for our free and/or premium services. We do not share/sell/transfer/give away etc our users email addresses! We hate spam as much as you do and only ever send email to you at account verification or if you want to recover account.
  * Browser language settings as sent to us by your browser may be used for the duration of the session to display the site in your preferred language.

* * *

###  3rd Party Payment processors (who you might encounter if upgrading to a premium account) 

filecloud.io uses services provided by 3rd party secure credit card payment processors such as 2checkout.com who collect information when you place an order in order to process the order and minimise fraud, [click here for 2checkout.com privacy policy](https://www.2checkout.com/privacy/)   

* * *

###  3rd Party Advertising and Analytics 

filecloud.io uses services provided by 3rd parties such as Google in order to help maintain free services for our users and gather website usage analytics data in order to improve the service. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of: [Google](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

**Google Advertising and the DoubleClick DART cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by [visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

**Google Analytics**   
This site (like the majority of internet sites) uses Google Analytics to provide us with statistics which we can use to improve this site. [Detailed privacy policy is available here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html). 

* * *
